http://www.brockport.edu/about/privacy

Main Page Content
Category Name:
Information Technology
Responsible Unit:
Library, Information, and Technology Services
Responsible VP:
Provost and VP for Academic Affairs
Adoption Date:
June 16, 2002
Last Revision Date:
August 22, 2015
Last Review Date:
Shared governance: none
Policy Statement
This policy describes Brockport's privacy practices regarding information collected
from visitors to this website. It also describes what data is collected and how that
information is used. Brockport may, at its sole discretion, change, modify, add, or
delete portions of this policy.
This website provides links to other websites that are not under Brockport's control
or governed by this policy. Because this privacy policy only applies to this site,
you should examine the privacy policy of any other website, including other State
sites that you access through this website.
We do not collect any personal information about you unless you provide that information
voluntarily by sending email or completing an online form. This policy is consistent
with the provisions of the Internet Security and Privacy Act, the Freedom of Information
Law, and the Personal Privacy Protection Law.
Purpose/Scope
Our Commitment to Privacy
This website is designed to make it easier and more efficient for individuals and
businesses to interact with The College at Brockport, State University of New York.
Like all online resources, we recognize that visitors to this website are concerned
about their privacy. Brockport is committed to preserving your privacy when visiting
this website.
Applicability
Definitions
The following definitions apply to terms used in this policy:
Terms such as "us," "we," "our" and "Brockport" refer to The College at Brockport, State University of New York.
"Our website" refers to all Web pages officially maintained by us within the brockport.edu domain
for our marketing efforts or to conduct our day-to-day business with our students,
alumni, faculty and staff. This term does not apply to personal or other unofficial
pages unrelated to our marketing efforts or our day-to-day business.
The following terms appear in italics throughout this policy:
Personal information: For purposes of this policy, "personal information" means any information concerning
a natural person which, because of name, number, symbol, mark, or other identifier,
can be used to identify that natural person.
User: shall have the meaning set forth in subdivision 8 of section 202 of the State Technology
Law.
Policy Procedures
Information Collected When You Visit This Website
When visiting this website, Brockport automatically collects and stores the following
information about your visit:
The Internet Protocol address. The Internet Protocol address is a numerical identifier
assigned either to your Internet service provider or directly to your computer, which
is used to direct Internet traffic to you;
The type of browser, its version and the operating system you used;
The date and time you visited this site;
The web pages or services you accessed at this site;
The website you visited prior to coming to this website;
The website you visit as you leave this website; and
If you downloaded a file, the file that was downloaded.
None of the foregoing information is deemed to constitute personal information by
the Internet Privacy and Security Act.
The College uses Google Analytics to automatically collect and aggregate this information
on many parts of the website. You can read how Google uses data when you visit our website.
The information collected is used to improve the content of the Brockport website
and to help us understand how our users interact with our website. This information
is collected for statistical analysis and to determine what information is of most
and least interest to our users. The information is not collected for commercial marketing
purposes, and Brockport does not sell or otherwise disclose the information collected
from our website for commercial marketing purposes.
Information Collected When You Email Us or Complete a Transaction
If at any time you email us, your email address and the contents of your email will
be collected. This includes not only text characters, but also any audio, video and
graphic information formats you send us.
Your email address and the information included in your message will be used to respond
to you, to address issues you identify, to improve this website, or to forward your
message to another SUNY or State agency for appropriate action. Your email address
is not collected for non-university commercial purposes, and we are not authorized
to sell or otherwise disclose your email address for non-university commercial purposes.
During your visit to the Brockport website you may take a survey, register for a class,
fill out an application, conduct a financial transaction, access an authenticated
file, complete an order form or complete an online form for some other purpose. We
will use the data you provide us during these transactions, including personal information,
to operate our programs, which may include the provision of goods, services and information.
The information collected by Brockport may be disclosed by Brockport for those purposes
that may be reasonably ascertained from the nature and terms of the transaction in
which the information was submitted.
We do not knowingly collect personal information from children or create profiles
of children through this website. Users are cautioned, however, that the collection
of personal information will be treated as though it was submitted by an adult.
Disclosure of Information Collected Through This Website
Information collected through this website, personal or otherwise, may, if not protected
by federal or state law, be subject to disclosure pursuant to law, such as the Freedom
of Information Law (FOIL), or court order.
Additionally, we may disclose personal information to federal or state law enforcement
authorities to enforce our rights against unauthorized access or attempted unauthorized
access to our information.
Finally, we may aggregate and disclose information collected through this website
using statistical techniques in a form that cannot be used to identify any particular
person. Such data might be publicly disclosed for the purposes of program evaluation.
Security
We are strongly committed to protecting personal information collected through our website against unauthorized access, use or disclosure. Confidentiality,
integrity, and availability of information are staples of our security goals which
drive our procedures. Consequently, we limit employee access to personal information from this website to only those employees who need access to perform a specific job.
Security measures have been integrated into the design, implementation and day-to-day
operations of this site as part of our continuing commitment to the security of electronic
content as well as the electronic transmission of information. Our procedures include,
but are not limited to, authentication, authorization, monitoring, auditing, and encryption.
NOTE: The information contained in this policy should not be construed in any way
as giving business, legal, or other advice, or warranting as fail proof, the security
of information provided via this website. For site security purposes and to ensure
that this website remains available to all users, we employ software to monitor traffic
to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information or otherwise cause
damage to this site.
Cookies
Cookies are simple text files stored by your Web browser to provide a means of distinguishing
among users of this website. The use of cookies is a standard practice among Internet
websites. Most often, cookies store a randomly generated identifying tag on the software
or hardware you use to access this website. The software and hardware you use to access
this website allows you to refuse new cookies or delete existing cookies.
We use cookies in the following ways to better serve you:
to verify authorized access to web systems that contain personal information (e.g. Blackboard, Banner);
to enhance or customize your visit to our website (e.g. to remember user preferences);
and
to better understand the use of our website so we can better serve users in the future.
To protect personal information, we may require users to accept cookies to access
certain online services. However, we do not require the use of cookies to access any
public areas of our website.
In addition, we use and share site analytics and data with various third-party services
for behavioral and remarketing campaigns. These marketing activities may involve:
showing online advertisements to users whose online habits have indicated a possible
interest in Brockport's academic programs;
showing online advertisements to users who have previously visited our website.
These third-party vendors may use cookies to track Internet use. Information gathered
by these cookies may be used to display Brockport advertisements on websites across
the Internet. To opt-out of receiving behavioral or remarketing messages from us,
you need to opt-out by using tools provided by various third-party vendors:
Google
Microsoft
Yahoo!
Links Disclaimer
In order to provide visitors with certain information, this website provides links
to local, state and federal government agencies, and websites of other organizations.
A link does not constitute an endorsement of the content, viewpoint, accuracy, opinions,
policies, products, services or accessibility of those websites. Once you visit another
website from this website, you are subject to the terms and conditions of that website,
including, but not limited to, its privacy policy.
Information Disclaimer
Information provided on this website is intended to allow visitors immediate access
to public information. While all attempts are made to provide accurate, current and
reliable information, we recognize the possibility of human and/or mechanical error.
Therefore, The College at Brockport, its employees, officers and agencies make no
representations as to the accuracy, completeness, currency or suitability of the information
provided by this site, and deny any expressed or implied warranty as to the same.
Links to Related Procedures and Information
There are no links for this policy at this time.
Contact Information
The College at Brockport may revise or update this Privacy Policy. Please contact
us as described below or check back at this site to obtain a copy of this Privacy
Policy.
For questions regarding this Internet privacy policy, please contact our privacy officer
via e-mail at privacy@brockport.edu or by regular mail at:
Privacy Compliance OfficerThe College at Brockport350 New Campus Dr.Brockport, NY 14420
History (in descending order)
